Guide to the Thomas Parran Papers, 1892-1968 UA.90.F14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photograph Collection, XLI.
  - Photograph taken on the occasion of the lunch offered on Thursday, February 25, 1937, in the building attached to the Palace of the Pan American Union, in honor of His Excellency Mr. Ricardo Castro Beeche, Minister of Costa Rica in the United States, by the Director General of the Pan American Union, Dr. L. S. Rowe
  - His Excellency Mr. Alfredo Busk Codas, Minister of the Republic of Paraguay in the United States, and the other guests who attended a lunch offered in honor of the Paraguayan diplomat by Dr. L. S. Rowe, Director General of the Pan American Union, Thursday, June 25, 1936
  - Photograph taken at the Annex of the Panamerican Union, Thursday, October 2, 1941, on the occasion of the luncheon offered in honor of His Excellency Mr. Fernand Dennis, Minister of Haiti in the United States, by the Director General of the Union Pan American, Dr. L. S. Rowe
  - Dr. Thomas Parran Jr. and six others
  - Dr. Thomas Parran Jr. and six others
  - Thomas Parran with a Priest, two children and three others, Rochester, 1930
  - Polio Conference, New York, Dorill, Godfrey, and Parran, 1931
  - Thomas Parran with five unidentifed others
  - Thomas Parran and unidentified guest in his office
  - Thomas Parran and unidentified guest in his office
  - Thomas Parran and unidentified guest in his office
  - Thomas Parran and unidentified guest in his office
  - Thomas Parran and unidentified guest in his office
  - Unidentified portrait by Walmsley Leuhard, 1939
  - Thomas Parran speaking in front of a crowd
  - Autographed Portrait, Jult 21, 1947
  - Autographed Portrait
  - Autographed Portrait, 1939
  - Autographed Portrait - A. Francis
- Scrapbooks, XLII.
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 1804)
  - Scrapbook, 1934 (Oversize 1, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Oversize 1, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1941-1943 (Oversize 2, Volume 3)
  - "Surgeon General", By G. Edward Pendray (Oversize 2, Volume 4)
  - Mr. Thomas Parran - Newspaper Publicity, 1937-1938 (Oversize 2, Folder 1805)
  - Scrapbook, 1933 (Oversize 2, Volume 5)
  - Dr. Thomas Parran, Surgeon General of the U.S. Public Health Service, 1944 (Oversize 2, Volume 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1935 (Oversize 3, Volume 7)
  - Scrapbook, 1936-1937 (Oversize 3, Volume 8)